[
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/000-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/000-front.webp",
    "number": 0
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/001-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/001-front.webp",
    "number": 1
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/002-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/002-front.webp",
    "number": 2
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/003-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/003-front.webp",
    "number": 3
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/004-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/004-front.webp",
    "number": 4
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/005-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/005-front.webp",
    "number": 5
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/006-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/006-front.webp",
    "number": 6
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/007-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/007-front.webp",
    "number": 7
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/008-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/008-front.webp",
    "number": 8
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/009-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/009-front.webp",
    "number": 9
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/010-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/010-front.webp",
    "number": 10
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/011-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/011-front.webp",
    "number": 11
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/012-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/012-front.webp",
    "number": 12
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/013-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/013-front.webp",
    "number": 13
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/014-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/014-front.webp",
    "number": 14
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/015-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/015-front.webp",
    "number": 15
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/016-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/016-front.webp",
    "number": 16
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/017-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/017-front.webp",
    "number": 17
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/018-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/018-front.webp",
    "number": 18
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/019-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/019-front.webp",
    "number": 19
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/020-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/020-front.webp",
    "number": 20
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/021-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/021-front.webp",
    "number": 21
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/022-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/022-front.webp",
    "number": 22
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/023-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/023-front.webp",
    "number": 23
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/024-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/024-front.webp",
    "number": 24
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/025-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/025-front.webp",
    "number": 25
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/026-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/026-front.webp",
    "number": 26
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/027-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/027-front.webp",
    "number": 27
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/028-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/028-front.webp",
    "number": 28
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/029-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/029-front.webp",
    "number": 29
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/030-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/030-front.webp",
    "number": 30
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/031-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/031-front.webp",
    "number": 31
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/032-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/032-front.webp",
    "number": 32
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/033-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/033-front.webp",
    "number": 33
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/034-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/034-front.webp",
    "number": 34
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/035-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/035-front.webp",
    "number": 35
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/036-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/036-front.webp",
    "number": 36
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/037-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/037-front.webp",
    "number": 37
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/038-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/038-front.webp",
    "number": 38
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/039-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/039-front.webp",
    "number": 39
  },
  {
    "back": "./cards/imgs/cards/040-back.webp",
    "front": "./cards/imgs/cards/040-front.webp",
    "number": 40
  }
]
